Guide to the J. B. Fuqua Papers, 1929-2006 and undated RL.00426
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession 2008-0024
  - Home Office Files
    - CNN YOUR HEALTH SHOW 3/2/02 Video tape, 2002 (Box 102-104)
      J.B. Fuqua (and Tom Johnson) profiled/interviewed.
    - Junior Achievement JB Fuqua (Accepted on his behalf by Ann Sterechi with Paul Ostergard), JA National Business Hall Fame 2002, 2002 (Box 102-104)
      A retrospective on J.B. Fuqua precedes giving award.
    - Fuqua Center Dedication Hampden-Sydney Collection. Video tape - Dedication of the Fuqua International Communications Center at Hampden-Sydney College, 2006 (Box 102-104)
      Speech by Fuqua regarding the global economy.
    - Fuqua Center for Late-Life Depression: Living Well: The Truth About Depression Video - Informational/Promotional program (Box 102-104)
    - Aging With Grace: The Ministry of Wesley Woods Video tape - Informational/Promotional program (Box 102-104)
    - NATIONAL LONGEVITY RESOURCE CENTER - National Park Seminary Historic District Video, 2002 (Box 102-104)
    - Four (4) copies of DUKE: THE FUQUA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS Video tape - promotional tape sent to 1994 incoming class, 1992 (Box 105-106)
      May be duplicate of promotional tapes already at the Fuqua Business School
    - DUKE UNIVERSITY, FUQUA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS ROBERT A. WILSON ASSOCIATES, 2-28-92 Video tape - Not-mass-produced version of same promotional tape above (item 266), 1992 (Box 105-106)
    - Four (4) copies of DUKE: THE FUQUA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS Promotional tape, 1994 (Box 105-106)
    - Five (5) copies of Celebrating 25 Years: DUKE: THE FUQUA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS (Box 105-106)
    - Three (3) copies of TV Interview, Ostankino TV Station, Moscow, Russia, September 21, 1993 (Box 105-106)
    - Six (6) copies of FUQUA B.O.V. DINNER 4-14-89 Video tape - Tape of Board of Visitors Dinner, 1989 (Box 105-106)
      Speech given by J.B. Fuqua.
    - FUQUA B.O.V. DINNER DUB 4/14/89 Video tape - Home-made (?) Duplicate of the Board of Visitors Dinner tape above, 1989 (Box 105-106)
      Speech given by J.B. Fuqua
    - FSB BOARD OF VISITORS DINNER - 4/14/89 $4Mil Gift Announcement Audio Cassette tape, 1989 (Box 105-106)
    - Cumberland College Awards Presentation - 1996 Video tape - awarding of the J.B. Fuqua Excellence in Teaching Award at Cumberland College, 1996 (Box 105-106)
      A cursory review shows no direct comment regarding Fuqua
    - The Honorable Terry Sanford Remembered Video tape, 1998 (Box 105-106)
    - Dub of segment on prices in the Soviet Union, Moneyline, 1/2/92, CNN, 7 pm Video tape, 1992 (Box 105-106)
    - Fuqua Business School with Sprint International: Training Russian Managers Video tape - Russian language program about Center for Manager Training from the former Soviet Union at Duke/Fuqua (Box 105-106)
    - CNN 3/25/92 - Fuqua School program for managers from the former Soviet Union Video tape, 1992 (Box 105-106)
      Details about Fuqua's program for managers from former Soviet Union.
    - Celebrate Fuqua 1998 Video tape - tape of images and music celebrating Fuqua Values, 1998 (Box 105-106)
    - SHATALIN - FSB 10-5-90 Video tape - recording of event welcoming a Mr. Shatalin from the Soviet Union in association with Fuqua's Center for Soviet Management Development, 1990 (Box 105-106)
    - Russia: Facing the Future Carnegie Corporation Video tape - Judy Woodruff hosted informative program (Box 105-106)
    - Thomas Center Video tape - Recording of the dedication of the R. David Thomas Center, 1989 (Box 105-106)
      J.B. Fuqua present, awarded as a donor, and gave speech at outdoor dedication.
      Existence and Location of Copies note
      Use Copies: DVD use copy available
    - USSR FSB 4/90 Video tape - Recording of visit and speech by Soviet Ambassador, 1990 (Box 105-106)
    - FSB Video tape - A comic video invitation to a class of the Fuqua school to Gallo Industries employment informational meeting (Box 105-106)
    - Soviet Ambassador Yuri Dubinin 4-17-90, 1990 (Box 105-106)
      J.B. Fuqua present and introduces Ambassador Dubinin.
    - GROUND BREAKING CEREMONIES FOR THE R. DAVID THOMAS CENTER, FUQUA BUSINESS SCHOOL, DUKE UNIV., MAY 9, 1987, 1987 (Box 105-106)
      Prof. done by Duke Studios, J.B. Fuqua present and gave a speech at the outdoor ground breaking
    - Vladimir Chelnokov, Sept. 1991 - Moscow Video tape - Recording of interview with past participant in Fuqua program for managers from the former Soviet Union, 1991 (Box 105-106)
    - MOSCOW TV 9/94, JBF - Shoe store Video tape - Russian-language news clip featuring J.B. Fuqua, 1994 (Box 105-106)
    - FUQUA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS - KELER DEDICATION, March 22, 1996 Video tape - Celebration of Dean Keler, 1996 (Box 105-106)
      J.B. Fuqua present, but gave no speech.
    - Fuqua School of Business Building Dedication Video tape - recording of dedication of Fuqua School building, 1983 (Box 105-106)
      J.B. Fuqua present and gave a speech.
    - R. David Thomas News Coverage (3 Parts) 6/13/86 Video tape - News reports regarding Thomas' contribution to Duke for Fuqua's Thomas Center, 1986 (Box 105-106)
    - Nightly Business Report 4/22/91 (Fuqua-MBA Games) Video tape - Short report at end of show about MBA Games held at Fuqua, 1991 (Box 105-106)
    - FUQUA - MBA Games 1991 Video tape - recording including NBR report above (item 292) and additional footage from the MBA Games 1991, 1991 (Box 105-106)
    - J.B. Fuqua 2/8/88 FUQUA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS Video tape - FSB Speaker Series, 1988 (Box 105-106)
    - DUKE: THE FUQUA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS: A VISION OF GENEROSITY Video tape (Box 105-106)
      Profile/History of J.B. Fuqua with emphasis on his generosity.
    - 10 minute Alumni tape 1995 Video tape - Cumberland College Cumberland Today program to inform Alumni of what is going on at Cumberland, 1995 (Box 105-106)
    - DUKE: THE FUQUA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS: THROUGH THE YEARS Video tape - Information program outlining the history of the business at Duke including appearances by J.B. Fuqua (Box 105-106)
    - THE DUKE MBA FALL 2000 Video tape - Informative program regarding Fuqua School of Business and its MBA degree for materials,2000 (Box 105-106)
    - COLORCRAFT VIP TRIP FALL 1980 Video tape - Could not get to play, 1980 (Box 107-109)
      Could not get to play/could not review.
    - COLORCRAFT REUNION, NOVEMBER 5-197, 1999 Video tape - Group having reunion weekend and touring Fuqua Conservatory, 1999 (Box 107-109)
      No direct comment regarding Fuqua
    - AJAY TELEVISION NETWORK Video tape - A Montage of the beginnings of numerous shows and Octa-Gym/AJAY (a Fuqua Industries Co.) commercials (Box 107-109)
    - SNAPPER, HENCO ADVERTISING AGENCY Video tape - Collection of commercials by/for numerous banks, 1987? (Box 107-109)
      Includes an inventory of the commercials and when/where they aired
    - Glaxo R&D Tour Video tape - Informational program about the Glaxo Research Institute (Box 107-109)
      No direct comment regarding Fuqua, maybe something he was viewing for business purposes
    - Qualex: A CONVERSATION WITH BOB HUNTZINGER Video tape - Interview with photographer associated with the Sports Illustrated "Swimsuit" issue (Box 107-109)
      Video put together by photo processing company, Qualex
    - QUALEX, INC. PHOTO FINISHING TOUR Video tape - Informational program on photo processing by Qualex, 1989 (Box 107-109)
    - QUALEX PLANT FOOTAGE Video tape, 1989 (Box 107-109)
      Tape seems damaged, could not get to rewind
    - Two (2) copies of CBS SPECIAL REPORT! THIS WEEK IN ATLANTA Video tape - Report on Snappers advertising, 1985 (Box 107-109)
    - SNAPPER, SNAPPER PRODUCTS BUY GEORGIA FIRST SPOT Video tape - 30 second commercial highlighting Snapper's Georgia Factory/Connection, 1988 (Box 107-109)
    - COLORCRAFT VIDEO PRESENTATION 11/85 Video tape - Informational program on Colorcraft, 1985 (Box 107-109)
    - THE CARTERS: A CONVERSATION PTS 1 & 2 Video tape - Georgia Public Broadcasting Program on ex-President Jimmy Carter and family, 2002 (Box 107-109)
    - AJAY ADVERTISING REEL 8/15/85 Video tape - Montage of the beginnings of numerous shows and AJAY exercise equipment (a Fuqua Industries Co.) commercials, 1985 (Box 107-109)
    - Scotch 542 Dictating Cassette Audio Cassette (Box 107-109)
    - FUQUA Sony HF Audio Cassette (Box 107-109)
    - AMR international, inc. Rate of Return on Investment Audio Cassette collection, 1972 (Box 107-109)
      Not reviewed, 12 audiocassettes in wooden case.
    - REPUBLIC ENERGY CORPORATION MISSISSIPPI INDEX, Roll 3 Film reel (Box 107-109)
    - THE FUQUA STORY Film reel (Box 107-109)
    - SNAPPER TILLER Cart-Reel MoviePak, 1976 (Box 107-109)
    - NATIONAL TV SPOTS Cart-Reel MoviePak, 1975 (Box 107-109)
    - SNAPPER RIDER MOWER Cart-Reel MoviePak, 1977 (Box 107-109)
    - SNAPPER V SERIES WALK BEHIND MOWER Cart-Reel MoviePak, 1977 (Box 107-109)
    - GEORGIA-PACIFIC TELEVISION: FUQUA INDUSTRIES 1987 FIRST QUARTER SLIDE #40 Tape, 1987 (Box 107-109)
    - GEORGIA-PACIFIC TELEVISION: FUQUA INDUSTRIES NEW YORK TELECONFERENCE Tape (Box 107-109)
    - FUQUA INDUSTRIES, INC. COLORCRAFT 1/85 Tape, 1985 (Box 107-109)
    - editel Chicago AJAY ENTERPRISES OCTA-GYM Tape, 1984 (Box 107-109)
    - OPRYLAND PRODUCTIONS: HENCO ADVERTISING - SNAPPER Tape (Box 107-109)
    - Larry King Weekend, May 31, 1997 COPY Video tape - Episode of Larry King with Robert Schuller as guest, 1997 (Box 110-113)
    - Two (2) Copies of NIGHTLY BUSINESS REPORT, FEBRUARY 21, 1991 Video tape - coverage of impending ground war in the First Gulf War, 1991 (Box 110-113)
      Profile on/Interview with Corp Management Efficiency and Productivity and other topics.
    - FUQUA PROFILE Video tape - portion of an monologue by Fuqua about his philanthropy (Box 110-113)
    - GEORGIA-PACIFIC TELEVISION: J.B. Fuqua media interviews Video tape - Montage of interviews by J.B. Fuqua on multiple shows (Box 110-113)
    - SNAPPER LAS VEGAS DEALER DEMO 1/10/95 Video tape - Informational program by Snapper, 1995 (Box 110-113)
    - Two (2) copies of SNAPPER Land Toy/Power tools… Video tape - Collection of Snapper commercials, 1990 (Box 110-113)
    - SNAPPER Power Tools Current Equipment… Video tape - Collection of Snapper commercials, 1990 (Box 110-113)
    - SNAPPER 'LIBERTY' Video tape - Informational program about the Statue of Liberty, immigration to the U.S., and History of Southern Saw Works/Snapper (Box 110-113)
    - GEORGIA PUBLIC TV MONEYLINE 2/11/86 Interview with Mr. Fuqua Video tape, 1986 (Box 110-113)
    - Two (2) copies of Ernst & Whinney/Atlanta Business Chronicle Biggest/Best Deals of 1986 Luncheon. Speaker: Mr. J.B. Fuqua Video tape, 1987 (Box 110-113)
      J.B. Fuqua Keynote speaker at event.
    - CYBERVISION 'PROFILES OF ACHIEVEMENT' TRT 50:10 Video tape - Profile of Kimmens Wilson (Box 110-113)
    - GEORGIA EDUCATIONAL MEDIA SERVICES: Secretaries in Conference Video tape - Southern Center for International Studies program with former U.S. Secretaries of State (Box 110-113)
    - Two (2) Copies of GEORGIA-PACIFIC TELEVISION: J.B. Fuqua Interviews Tape (Box 110-113)
    - DUB Georgia Public TV: GA M'Line J.B. Fuqua Tape (Box 110-113)
    - INSERT Georgia Public TV: Georgia Moneyline, Fuqua Interview Tape, 1986 (Box 110-113)
    - COLORCRAFT PRESENTATION- GENERIC Video tape - Informational program on Color Craft, 1985 (Box 110-113)
      May be duplicate.
    - INTERVIEW WITH JB FUQUA, FINANCIAL NEWS, FNN-TV, FEBRUARY 24, MONDAY, 1:30PM Video tape - interview with Fuqua on Financial News Network (Box 110-113)
    - FRICKS ADV, 12/30/94 Video tape - Collection of three (3) Snapper TV advertisement, 1994 (Box 110-113)
    - Three (3) copies of JB FUQUA CNN-196:30-197:30PM 12/25/83 30 minute interview Video tape - Interview with Fuqua on Inside Business, 1983 (Box 110-113)
    - Four (4) copies of JB FUQUA PINNACLE CNN- 2-1-83 (145) Video tape - profile of Fuqua on CNN Business News Pinnacle with interview of Fuqua, 1983 (Box 110-113)
    - MAKOVSKY & COMPANY INC. BUSINESS TIMES MANAGEMENT REPORT & BUSINESS TIMES Style/J.B. Fuqua Ramsey 12/22/84 Companies/Fuqua Sowers 1/3/85 Video tape - Report on Fuqua Industry's trend toward acquiring businesses, 1984-1985 (Box 110-113)
    - Four (4) Copies JBF 12/85 7:30 Magazine Video tape- Atlanta 730 program containing profile on Fuqua including interview material, 1985 (Box 110-113)
    - GEORGIA-PACIFIC TELEVISION: J.B. Fuqua Interviews Video tape - Collection of 6 television shows with segments about Fuqua, 1983-86 (Box 110-113)
      This tape contains a number of interviews/programs that appear separately on other tapes.
    - ViP J. B. Fuqua Interviews Video tape - Four (4) copies of same collection of TV segments found on GEORGIA-PACIFIC TELEVISION: J.B. Fuqua Interviews Video tape (item 2348), 1983-1986 (Box 110-113)
      Contains a number of interviews/programs that appear separately on other tapes.
    - JBF INTERVIEW ON WJBF-TV Video tape - Interview with JB Fuqua with remarks from prior speeches, 1990 (Box 110-113)
    - JB FUQUA Rotary Club - Augusta Video tape - Recording of speech by Fuqua at Rotary Club, 1986 (Box 110-113)
    - JB FUQUA OF FUQUA INDUSTRIES, FINANCIAL NEWS NETWORK, FNN-TV, FEB 3, MON, 12 NOON (Box 110-113)
    - The Bulls Meet The Bear Video tape - Program on conversion of Russia to Free-market system (Box 110-113)
      A cursory review shows no direct comment regarding Fuqua, Russia connection.
    - $4 million - news report Re Russia Studies Video tape - 10 second TV News program comment on Fuqua's contribution to bring Russian managers to U.S. (Box 110-113)
    - Various interviews Video tape - Collection of assorted interviews/TV programs on Fuqua, Various (Box 110-113)
      These TV interviews/segments are also on other tapes (see items 348 & 349).
    - Mr. J.B. Fuqua 6-April-00 Video tape - Fuqua International School of Christian Communication with speech by Fuqua, 2000 (Box 110-113)
    - BUSINESS PROFILES J.B. FUQUA Video tape - Robert Schuller Hour of Power Video tape with J.B. Fuqua as guest (Box 110-113)
      Discussion of the Russian project, perhaps this was taped over another program?
    - 'Friends Do More' Atlanta Union Mission 13:00 Video tape - Informational program on Atlanta Union Mission and its newest residential hall Fuqua Hall (Box 110-113)
      Fuqua funded a Hall that is part of this Mission.
    - CBS NEWS SUNDAY MORNING 8/4/02 TRT: (11 min.) - News report on Airshow, 2002 (Box 110-113)
      Cursory review shows no direct comment regarding Fuqua.
    - GREAT AMERICAN COOKIE COMPANY S.O.A.R. 44:00 Video tape - Michael Coles biking from Savannah to San Diego Informational Program (Box 110-113)
    - PBS CEO Exchange 12-3-00 Video tape - Episode of PBS's CEO Exchange filmed at Fuqua School, 2000 (Box 110-113)
    - 'MONEYMAKERS IV' SHOW #413 SUCCESS STORY: MAKING IT IN THE 80'S Video tape - interview with Fuqua, 1985 (Box 110-113)
    - Makovsky & Company Fuqua Interview PBS Stations 2/1/84 Video tape - Interview with JB Fuqua, 1984 (Box 110-113)
    - Three (3) copies of GEORGIA-PACIFIC TELEVISION: J. B. Fuqua media interviews Video tape - Multiple different TV interviews done by Fuqua (Box 110-113)
    - EXCHANGE CLUB J.B. FUQUA Video tape - Speech by Fuqua at Exchange Club (Box 110-113)
    - JBF-'Profile' Ch. 8 WGTV 11/84 Video tape - Georgia Money-Line episode containing profile of J.B. Fuqua, 1984 (Box 110-113)
      May be on other compilation of interview tapes.
    - J. B. FUQUA PARTY 10/24/98 Tape, 1988 (Box 114-116)
    - OGLETHORPE UNIVERSITY COMMENCEMENT ADDRESS BY J.B. FUQUA May 18, 1986 Tape, 1986 (Box 114-116)
      Not reviewed, see video tape 411.
    - FUQUA ANALYSES MEETING- HOUSTON 3-12-1968 Reel-to-Reel Tape, 1968 (Box 114-116)
    - Commencement Address by Mr. J. B. Fuqua Hampden-Sydney College May 29, 1972 Reel-to-reel tape, 1972 (Box 114-116)
    - WJBF RADIO DEDICATION Cassette tape (Box 114-116)
    - WGAC 580 KHZ DEDICATION 1946 Cassette tape (Box 114-116)
    - JB Fuqua - Snapper 7-27-83 Cassette tape, 1983 (Box 114-116)
    - J.B. FUQUA 7/27/83 SNAPPER Distributors meet Cassette tape, 1983 (Box 114-116)
    - JB FUQUA 7/27/83 Snapper Distributors meeting Cassette tape, 1983 (Box 114-116)
    - 1972 stockholders meet 4/17/72 - FQA Cassette tape, 1972 (Box 114-116)
    - Rotary Club 08/24/98 George Heery Cassette tape, 1998 (Box 114-116)
    - Atlanta Financial Executives 11/22/83 Cassette tape, 1983 (Box 114-116)
    - History of Fuqua Industries, 1967-1978, Company acquisitions, etc. Cassette tape (Box 114-116)
    - Special committee Cassette tape (Box 114-116)
    - 3 copies of Fuqua School, The Beginning of a Great New Tradition Video tape - news clip about JB Fuqua donating to the Prince Edward Academy, having the school named after him, and a speech/press conference with him, 1993 (Box 114-116)
    - 3 copies of Fuqua School, The Beginning of a Great New Tradition *The First Day of School* Video tape - Footage from the first day at the newly re-named Fuqua School including an assembly with a speech by J.B. Fuqua, 1993 (Box 114-116)
    - 2 copies of Fuqua School Farmville, Virginia Video tape - Informational tape on Fuqua School (Box 114-116)
    - ROBERT A. WILSON ASSOCIATES, INC. FUQUA SCHOOL ROUGH CUT Video tape - Rough of one of the Fuqua School informational programs listed above (Box 114-116)
      Final version of info tape in earlier box (item 266?).
    - Fuqua School Fuqua Interview Video tape - News report on the Fuqua school Russian Managers Program followed by a short interview with Fuqua about the program (Box 114-116)
    - WJBF-TV 40TH ANNIVERSARY PROGRAM NOV. 27, 1993 Video tape - TV channel history program including old and more recent footage with J.B. Fuqua, 1993 (Box 114-116)
    - An Invitation: Prince Edward County and the Town of Farmville invite business and industry to explore the 'Opportunities of the Heart of Virginia' Video tape - Informational program on Prince Edward County area (Box 114-116)
    - Fuqua School Homecoming Parade 1993 Video tape - home (style) video of a parade, 1993 (Box 114-116)
    - ATLANTA ROTARY CLUB MEETING MARCH 9, 1987 SPEAKER: MR. J.B. FUQUA. ORIGINAL TAPE NOT EDITED Video tape, 1987 (Box 114-116)
    - Two (2) copies of ATLANTA ROTARY CLUB MEETING MARCH 9, 1987 SPEAKER: MR. J.B. FUQUA. EDITED COPY Video tape, 1987 (Box 114-116)
    - Small Business Person of the Year Award Breakfast J.B. Fuqua, Speaker 11/5/90 - Sheraton Hotel, Augusta, GA Video tape - Fuqua's speech at an awards ceremony, 1990 (Box 114-116)
    - Reunion 5/2/87 Video tape - Recording of Dorothy Fuqua's 1987 class reunion, 1987 (Box 114-116)
    - Prospect Class Reunion May 11, 1990 Video tape - semi-professional recording of a 17 year reunion hosted by J.B. Fuqua, 1990 (Box 114-116)
    - 8-23-93 FUQUA SCHOOL NEWS CLIPS WRIC WTVR WWBT Video tape - collection of five news clips about renaming of Prince Edward Academy including footage of Fuqua announcement speech, 1993 (Box 114-116)
    - 6-28-91 Fuqua Stockholders Meeting Video tape - Recording of Fuqua Industries Stockholder meeting at time of deconglomeration, 1990 (Box 114-116)
      A cursory review shows no appearance or speech by Fuqua.
    - Computer-Based Training versus Human Training featuring Fuqua School Technology Club Video tape - Fuqua School students call in to show Screen savers to voice off on topic of computer teaching, 1998 (Box 114-116)
    - Untitled video tape - collection of historic informational programs (Box 114-116)
      Includes J.B. Fuqua on his history with Lyndon B Johnson.
    - Mr. J.B. Fuqua Interview With Messrs. Henry and Karlton Howard September 24, 2004, WJBF-TV/Augusta, Georgia Video tape - regarding Parade of Quartets TV program, 2004 (Box 114-116)
    - Parade of Quartets 9/04 Video tape - A rough, uncut version of Mr. J.B. Fuqua Interview With Messrs. Henry and Karlton Howard September 24, 2004, WJBF-TV/Augusta, Georgia Video tape, 2004 (Box 114-116)
      Duplicate/uncut of item 398 above.
    - COPIES OF AUGUSTA COLLEGE'S SHOW 'AUGUSTA ALIVE' STUDENT PRODUCED Video tape - Five episodes of College student produced TV program (Box 114-116)
    - WJBF-TV 40th Anniversary Show Video tape - home recording of 40th anniversary program, 1993 (Box 114-116)
      Program on this tape on video tapes above (see item 386).
    - JB FUQUA & BOB YOUNG 40th ANNIVERSARY Video tape - Tape of interview that appears on WJBF-TV 40th Anniversary Program, 1993 (Box 114-116)
      Program on this tape appears (at least in part) on video tapes above (see item 386).
    - J. B. Fuqua and Bob Young 'IT'S THIS WAY', WJBF-TV FEBRUARY 11, 1990 Video tape - Interview with J.B. Fuqua with footage from other venues, 1990 (Box 114-116)
      Program on this tape appears on other video tapes.
    - J.B. FUQUA WJBF-TV REUNION PARTY AUGUSTA, GA - OCTOBER 24, 1998 Video Tapes - Speech by J.B. Fuqua at WJBF Reunion Party, 1998 (Box 114-116)
      Includes typed version of speech given on tape.
    - Alan FUQUA on Ann McKnights' Woman's World April 1966 - WJBF-TV Augusta Video tape - Program regarding students coming up with their own Code of Conduct at Langford, 1966 (Box 114-116)
    - J.B. Fuqua Speech Davis Award and B-Roll Video tape - Recording of Rotary Club speech, 1986 (Box 114-116)
      Speech on this tape appears on video tape above (see item 351).
    - Three (3) copies of HARVARD BUSINESS SCHOOL CLUB OF ATLANTA BUSINESS STATESMAN DINNER HONORING J.B. FUQUA, CHARIMAN, FUQUA INDUSTRIES DUPLICATE COPY OF MASTER TAPE Video tape - Recording of dinner honoring Fuqua including speech by Fuqua himself, 1987 (Box 114-116)
    - MR. J.B. FUQUA SPEAKING AT THE MARILYN L. TAYLOR SCHOOL OF BUSINESS, THE UNIV. OF KANSAS. DUPLICATE COPY OF ORIGINAL TAPE Video tape - Speech by Fuqua on fun side of building a business, 1987 (Box 114-116)
    - MEETING FOR FRIENDSHIP 5/90 US Video tape - Narrated Recording Fuqua World Trade Corp. representatives meeting with Chinese Gov. officials, 1990 (Box 114-116)
    - J.B. Fuqua Univ. of Kansas Presentation March, 1987 MASTER #1 of 1 Video tape - Unedited copy of event at which Fuqua spoke at Univ. of KS Business School, 1987 (Box 114-116)
      Speech by Fuqua on this tape on tape above (see item 408), note from desk of Leslie Adams included asking Bob to make 2 edited copies.
    - Oglethorpe University Commencement - May 18, 1986 Address given by: Mr. J.B. Fuqua Video tape - awarding of honorary law degree to and speech by Fuqua, 1986 (Box 114-116)
    - AISD Strategic Action Planning Team Presents Peter Lewis Video tape - Presentation by New York Times columnist in Austin (Box 114-116)
    - Oglethorpe Video tape - seems to be blank (Box 114-116)
    - DONNA L. BROWNING DIRECTOR OF PUBLIC RELATIONS Business card video tape - News reports on Atlanta Mounted Police (Box 114-116)
    - GEORGIA-PACIFIC TELEVISION FUQUA INDUSTRIES Presentation to NEW YOUR SOCIETY OF SECURITY ANALYSTS April 1987 Video tape, 1987 (Box 114-116)
      J.B. Fuqua presented/spoke at the event.
    - JB FUQUA U. of Georgia Broadcast speech 1979 Video tape - award presentation to and speech by Fuqua, 1979 (Box 114-116)
    - First Pennsylvania Bank THEMES ON CORPORATE FINANCE MR. FUQUA 'CREATING SHAREHOLDER VALUE' Video tape - interview with Fuqua (Box 114-116)
    - Three (3) copies of DOROTHY CHAPMAN FUQUA CONSERVATORY DINNER. MARCH 5 1989 Audio cassette, 1989 (Box 117-119)
    - Oglethorpe University Commencement - May 18, 1986 Address given by: Mr. J.B. Fuqua Tape #1, 1986 (Box 117-119)
      Not reviewed, tape 1.
    - Oglethorpe University Commencement - May 18, 1986 Address given by: Mr. J.B. Fuqua Tape #2, 1986 (Box 117-119)
      Not reviewed, tape 2.
    - Oglethorpe University Commencement - May 18, 1986 Address given by: Mr. J.B. Fuqua Tape #3, 1986 (Box 117-119)